david-eisner.com 2017-12-27

# Terms And Conditions

**TOS | Earnings Disclaimer | Privacy Policy | Contact**

PAXMAN LLC These terms presented herein are valid for any and all web pages on the domain backpackbusinessman.com and any site controlled by PAXMAN LLC that links to this page.

 **Privacy Policy**

Last Updated April, 2016   
Privacy Notice Table Of Contents:

    Our Commitment To Privacy  
    The Information We Collectlis  
    How We Use Information  
    Our Commitment To Data Security  
    Our Commitment To Children’s Privacy  
    How To Access Or Correct Your Information  
    How To Contact Us

Our Commitment To Privacy Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

The Information We Collect: This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on any PAXMAN LLC website including (but not limited to) backpackbusinessman.com. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

        Name 

        Address 

        Email address 

        Phone number 

        Credit/Debit Card Information 

    (etc.)

On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you will need to submit the recipient’s address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are:

        Name 

        Address 

        Phone Number 

    (etc.)

The Way We Use Information: We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. If you enter an email address when you purchase an order or if you opt-in to receive  a free gift, we will add you to our mailing list. We may send you recommendations for you to buy things and if you do, we may receive a commission. We may also send you other information which we think may be helpful to you. If we offer gift-cards by which you can personalize a product you order for another person. Information you provide to us to create a gift-card is only used for that purpose, and it is only disclosed to the person receiving the gift. We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. You can register with our website if you would like to receive our newsletter as well as updates on our new products and services. We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

Our Commitment To Data Security To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

Our Commitment To Children’s Privacy: Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by contacting customer support at: http://davideisner.kayako.com We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

Third-Party Cookies And Behavioral Tracking Are Used On This Entire Website To learn more about opting in and opting-out, please see this: https://www.perfectaudience.com/privacy/index.html

Custom Audience Disclosure Landing on any page controlled by PAXMAN LLC may cause you to collect a cookie that will add you to a custom audience advertising campaign on Facebook.com. You may see ads displayed that are being paid for and controlled by PAXMAN LLC as a result of being part of a custom audience. Ads may appear on other websites besides Facebook.com.

  **How To Contact Us**

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please submit a support ticket by clicking [here](http://davideisner.kayako.com/).   PAXMAN LLC Address is readily available but not listed publicly on the website for privacy and spam purposes. If you would like to obtain the company’s address, you can contact us by [clicking here](http://davideisner.kayako.com/).  
Terms Of Service

 **Policies and Procedures

Refund Policy * All refunds will be processed within 7 days. *

**

PAXMAN LLC, reserves the right to cancel any order at any time if company sees fit. * 100% money back guarantee covers price of product only. * You have THIRTY (30) Days from the date of the original purchase to request a refund. Any request for a refund after a THIRTY (30) DAY time limit will not be processed. You may cancel at anytime after the initial THIRTY (30) Days has passed if you have future payments pending.

 **Customer Service** : Refund requests must be [submitted to customer support](http://davideisner.kayako.com/) to be considered valid.  
Earnings Disclaimer  
 **  
The Earnings Disclaimer** on this page is valid for ALL pages and posts hosted on the domain backpackbusinessman.com or any site controlled by PAXMAN LLC that links to this page, hereinafter, “This Site”. This Disclaimer supersedes any other texts or images published on This Site or and any site controlled by PAXMAN LLC that links to this page. Any report or claim of income published on This Site is for informational purposes only. No guarantees of income are being made on This Site at any time, regardless of colorful language. You may or may not make money in any business venture talked about on this site and any site controlled by PAXMAN LLC. Any results you see on this website are not typical.

That’s the legal speak – here’s my straight-talk to YOU as a person: I only believe that money is spent in exchange of VALUE. I don’t think making money needs to be hard, but it needs to be based on substance. In business and in marketing, you usually need to put in some work to see a payoff, even a small one. In fact, it’s usually only small payoffs (if any) that come at the beginning of your business venture. Succeeding at any business, online or otherwise, will most likely require investment and re-investment of your time, energy, and money. It will probably also require dedication, perseverance, and a strategy. The government requires me to state the obvious to cover my butt – but you know better and I know it. Strategic action partnered with a positive state of mind will go further than any guarantees (you know, the ones I’m not making).
